malecontravel.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy | Malecón TravelMalecón Travel

We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

**Why did you receive a mailing from us?**  
Our email marketing is permission based. If you received a mailing from us, our records indicate that (a) you have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us.

We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings. If you believe you have received unwanted, unsolicited emails sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to abuse@malecon.no for review.

**How can you stop receiving email from us?**  
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the SafeUnsubscribe™ or Update Profile links at the end of any email. 

**How we protect your privacy?**  
We use appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. 

**Sharing and Usage**  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone for their promotional use without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information, and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. 

**Use of Web Beacons**  
When we send you emails, we may include a web beacon to allow us to determine the number of people who open our emails. When you click on a link in an email, we may record this individual response to allow us to customize our offerings to you.

Web beacons collect only limited information, such as a cookie identifier, time and date of a page being viewed, and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides (the URL).

Web hen delivered via email. If you do not wish to receive Web Beacons via email, you will need to disable HTML images or refuse HTML (select Text only) emails via your email software.

Malecón recognizes that respecting user privacy over the Internet is of utmost importance. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site: http://www.MALECONTRAVEL.COM. The Site is operated by MALECÓN.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our site coordinator at travel@malecon.no or by postal mail to:

  * MALECÓN
  * GRENSEN 9 B
  * 0183 OSLO
  * NORWAY

In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to process an order, offer services that require registration, assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you.

Generally, MALECÓN requests identifying information when you:

  * Register on any of our web sites.
  * Place an order.
  * Provide feedback to an online survey or tell us about an idea or suggestion.
  * Participate in a rebate program, contest, or other promotional offer.
  * Request a SPECIAL SERVICE.
  * Request information or files from technical support or customer service.

In these instances, MALECÓN will ask for your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and other relevant information needed to provide you with these services. In all instances, if you receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to “unsubscribe” from these mailings at any time.

What MALECÓN Will Do With Your Information.  
If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by MALECÓN and will only be used by MALECÓN to support your customer relationship with us.

We will not add you to a mailing list, or newsletter without your registration for this service. We will only contact you if further information is required from you to complete a service.

**What Others May Do With Your Information.**  
MALECÓN does not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through our Site (such as your name or email address) to any outside organization for use in its marketing or solicitations.

From time to time MALECÓN may use agents or contractors who will have access to your personal information to perform services for MALECÓN (such as DATABASE MAINTENANCE, FURTHER EXAMPLES), however, they are required by us to keep the information confidential and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services for MALECÓN.

In addition, MALECÓN may also share aggregate information about its customers and its web site visitors to advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we might share that our users are x percent PCs users and y percent Macintosh users. None of this information, however, will contain personal, identifying information about our users.

MALECÓN On-line Store.  
The MALECÓN On-line Store is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your identifying information. If you choose, you can set up an account. This will allow you to have a customized order page for express ordering and to view your purchasing history.

To protect your privacy, we have designed the Sites to include certain steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections in an account.

You will always have access to this account information and can view it, update it or correct it at any time.  
To access your information, you will need to use a password.

When purchasing products through our web site, the order form will also ask you to provide a daytime telephone number. However, the telephone number is only used to quickly resolve questions related to an order, such as to clarify customer email addresses that are inactive, or entered incorrectly.

MALECONTRAVEL.COM does provide links to other sites. Other Internet sites and services have separate privacy and data collection practices. Once you leave WWW.MALECONTRAVEL.COM, MALECÓN cannot control, and has no responsibility for, the privacy policies or data collection activities at other sites.

At times, we will use a feature on your web browser to send your computer a “cookie”. We do not use cookies to retrieve any personal information from your computer. We only use cookies to learn ways to enhance our Sites, and to give you more personalized services while you’re on our web site. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is sent. However, some functions of the Sites will not function if you refuse cookies. These areas of our web site will have information posted about cookies, and when a cookie will be uploaded to your computer.

MALECÓN is sensitive to the heightened need to protect the privacy of children under the age of 13. The vast majority of the material on our web site is not intended for children and is not targeted towards children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect data from children and, if we learn that we have received personal data from a child, we will remove this information from our database.

MALECÓN may from time to time revise its privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information. Contacting Us. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy and/or the practices of our web site, you can write to:

  * MALECÓN
  * GRENSEN 9 B
  * 0183 OSLO
  * NORWAY

This policy was created March 2008. Last updated May 2012

Malecón – ¡Camínalo!™
